Thank you for watching!
And now, it's time for our host, Bananaman, to welcome you to Nogizaka Under Construction.
Thank you very much.
Seino Face!
Facial expression. A gag facial expression.
Iwamoto... what?
I wasn't informed.
Depends on how far you want to go.
So, Mr. Kimura, how many do we have today?
Nogizaka. Facial players.
That's right.
Nogizaka is the original winner of the Face Championship.
I see.
Faces are the most important part of an idol's performance.
That's why this time we held an inter-team competition in which teams competed in various events using only their faces!
The winning team is as good as you'd expect!
The losing team will be punished with a game so severe that their faces will be contorted.
Punishment games these days, huh?
The cream of the face method the other day was terrible, wasn't it?
We haven't seen Yamashita here recently, have we?
Yes, but I'm glad I didn't see him on the air.
That was class.
I'm going to play the New Year's game for the youngsters.
We have that kind of thing.
I'm also the queen of the good looks.
Yes, I am.
Team Iwashiwa is strong because we have a good face queen.
Thank you very much.
Yoda doesn't want to lose.
I won't lose.
Punishment games are so hard.
It was really hard to get the cream.
But Mr. Degawa is happiest on days when he's taking a bath with other comedians, dropping cute stuff on each other.
Ew.
Well then, let's get to it.
Let's play the first game.
Let's tell them with just our faces.
Papa-papa-pan.
You mean faces.
The game is to have your friends guess which of the 15 subjects you have a facial expression on your face.
One chance per person.
The team with the most correct answers gets 2 points.
First, the mountain team will take the challenge, and see how many correct answers the eight of us can get.
The very qualified judges... the face judge, Mr. Hashira-san... you won the face championship.
Thank you very much.
He was really strong when he was young.
Now he's going "lookism-lookism" and you're out of a job.
That's right.
Are you confident, Yamashita?
Yes, I do. I've been doing facial expressions for a long time.
Drama isn't about facial expressions.
You have to get that from him too.
There are similarities.
Let's use only our faces to tell the story.
Let's start with the subject.
321.
Oh, wow.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's very good.
Come on, Yoda.
Gold.
Awesome!
That's great!
I know exactly what you mean.
We've known each other for a long time.
It's really great.
So cool!
I'm doing the Tochigi Nishida impersonation that Tatsuya Ueshima is doing right now.
I don't have it
I don't have it.
Come on, Yoda!
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
LOL!
Oh, my God, that's disgusting.
Five, yes.
Delicious!
Correct answer
That's great.
I don't understand how you can tell.
He's in a long mood.
I didn't think I could do that.
Okay, I've checked the subject.
3.2.1.
Oh.
Yes, I'm sleepy.
I'm surprised you can tell.
I think it's from here, isn't it?
The mountain team is doing well so far.
The third one, Tsugui, can you convey the message with just your face?
Please answer me.
It's sparkling.
Too bad.
This one is indeed difficult.
That's a tough one.
What? Where'd all the blood go?
You scared the shit out of me.
I thought it was gone.
Oh, no, this isn't Magic Wraps.
Open it.
You'll have to check the answer.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Here we go.
What? Wait a minute.
Come on, answer me.
Shit.
Correct.
That went over really well.
Why are you laughing?
Then Shibata's face is all that's needed to convey the message.
Two, one.
Which one?
Well, it's hard.
Too bad.
Not spicy.
Not spicy. Nothing's spicy.
It's not spicy. Nothing's spicy. It might look that way if you think it is.
I couldn't guess if it was just a black face.
Can you put your voice in there for a second?
Can you listen to me for once?
You're not allowed to speak.
You can't speak in this game.
Look at me.
Let's try again!
Are you okay?
Is he okay?
Are you doing it?
I know you're doing it.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it!
Ei-chan.
This...
I hate this place untuk.
I wonder if he's doing it now.
The last one is after the end Yamashita Isayama Ei
Sour
So the Yama team got 5 out of 8 questions right!
If I got it wrong, I drank too much of the black meat. That black meat is a little too much.
This is just normal.
I've never had alcohol before, so I just expected it to taste like that.
I've already spoken once before, so I can't do anything because I'm not allowed to speak.
Five correct. Excellent.
No. 4, because I've been hyped up for a long time.
I don't know if I'm right too.
So we had a hastily arranged exhibition by Bananaman 3
I'll answer no, no, because I've been doing this longer than everyone else.
Wait, that's not all there is now!
I've been doing this for a long time, so I understand... but nothing like this comes to mind.
I don't know what you mean when you say that, because I don't know what I'm going to do right now, but I'm going to ask you right now, and you gave it to me.
You're the most incomprehensible guy I've ever met.
I guess anything... even if I leak my, uh, eight runs... it's still...
But he'll do it when it's open.
Did I really leak my shit?
What's with this face?
What's he looking at?
Okay, there's a rat.
No, no, no...
No, no, no, there's a rat.
What the hell is this? What are you looking at?
He's saying something.
Don't say it! Don't say it!
It smells like he's saying something.
There's feces in front of the car.
Correct.
Correct. Correct.
You know what I mean.
You know what I'm talking about.
It's actually a phenomenon that really pissed Mr. Hima off.
That's right.
And I'm like, "Wow, that's terrible," and I get in my car, and I forgot it, and I stepped on it, and I went...
I stepped on it and went out.
Like, I forgot it.
That's all I can say.
It's the only route.
Oh, I forgot it.
I didn't forget.
Next is the rock team. What can you say with just your face?
Let's do it! Let's tell them with our faces!
Three, two, one.
So cute! So cute!
I like it.
Yes, yes, yes!
I'll never forgive you.
Good answer.
Amazing.
That was amazing.
How did you know?
I don't know.
Because we've known each other so long.
Behind your back.
One more time.
I checked.
Please.
Two, one.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Which one is it?
Look out of the way.
That's great.
How do you not get it?
We've known each other a long time.
I don't know how you don't get it.
That's really great.
It's not that easy.
I'll never forgive you.
Iwachin got it right on the third one in a row.
Kubo, let's keep going!
Am I right?
That's great!
Three wins in a row, two more to go.
321...
It's hard...
Matsuo.
I think I know what you mean.
I remember now.
You're right.
Perfect.
It's going to be perfect.
Come on. Yay!
Are you all right now?
Three, two, one.
I know, I know.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I didn't want to be like you.
Lucky me.
Oh, thank God.
That's good.
Oh, that's great.
We've already lined this up.
Dotom's five correct answers in a row.
We're already tied with Yam's team.
Kaki, can you tell by the look on his face?
Three, two, one.
Come on!
Let's see... let's see...
That's it!
Here it is!
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is hard.
You've got to really give it your all, Myun-chan.
I'll do my best, Myun-chan.
I'll do my best.
Three, two, one.
What?
Good luck!
Yay!
Reversed.
Come on, last one.
Three, two, one.
Yeah! Start!
Shame on you!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Yes!
How many of these did I get wrong?
What was that persimmon?
What was it?
What was that?
What is it? I'm just saying.
But I don't know. What is it? I don't know.
What is it?
There's a lot of "what is it? There's a lot of them.
What is it? faces.
Yeah, they're... they're... they're intense. I know.
So, in this matchup.
Iwa's team wins by two points.
Cute faces are all over the place after that!
Iwa, you're in trouble!
Let's continue!
Hime-san, please!
Cute face race once in 10 seconds
One person from each team must do a task for one minute at a time.
at the same time for one minute.
But once every 10 seconds
you will hear a shutter sound.
at that time, you have to stop the work and
a cute expression in the face panel.
to make a cute face in the face panel.
The one who is more advanced in the end
gets points.
The first round was Iwamoto vs. Tsutsui
The race for the fastest azuki bean reflection
Do I have to smile?
Didn't I say that?
Because you have a cute face.
If it's a cute face, it's fine.
Then it doesn't have to be a smile.
I see... inappropriate cuteness.
There's something like that, too.
Even if it's inappropriate.
If it's judged as cute, it's okay.
If you make a face that's so amazingly cute
I'll give you two azuki beans
I'll give it to you.
I don't think she'll be so happy with just one azuki bean.
Also, azuki beans are very important.
What should I do?
Yamamoto, how are your chopstick skills?
I'm not that bad, but I'm surprised they're smaller than I thought.
Yes, azuki are small.
I'm scared!
What about Fukuzui?
I've never done it before either, but I'm losing, so I'll do my best.
That's right, it's a bad punishment for losing.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go!
10987654321
Yamamoto.
I can carry you just a little further.
Nice pace.
That's the iron.
Oh, here it comes.
How cute!
Kimura-san... the peaches might explode.
Are you sure the azuki beans are all right?
What should I do?
So cute!
There's not enough room, is there?
It's okay if you hold on to the end of the bean...
It's so cute!
Oh, no!
It's coming, it's coming!
One...
Kimura-san, you don't have to go that way.
Surprisingly, you can't catch them if you can't catch them.
3 They're coming, they're coming!
So cute!
All clear.
Oh, man, that's not good.
Buh-buh-buh... Azuki's on the gun... and Iwamoto's on the gun... and we're looking at cute faces from here on out.
But there's a chance we'll get a negative azukis, so here's the face.
Cute.
And Shibata in the back is cute, too.
The third one.
The fourth one.
What do you think?
They're both a little cute, but not too cute.
No, they must be really cute.
No, they're both cute.
They're cute, but it's okay, it's okay.
They're just barely there.
Keep in mind, this is a pretty harsh assessment.
Next...
Azuki, how's this?
Azuki, that's not normal.
The face is the same as before.
Azuki, I'm sorry, but the minus is the same.
No, no, no, it's cute, but it's not cute.
He's so cute!
It's not cute.
It's Rust.
Well, well...
How's the azuki?
It's okay, it's cute.
This kind of cuteness
Not just smiles, but variations.
Ah, the cat with the bad grass...
So the result remained the same, and the mountain team won!
In the second round, Yoda and Yakubo jumped rope against each other. The winner was decided by the number of jumps in one minute and the cuteness points in the photo.
Can I have a handicap for this? Can I have a handicap? I'm not as good a jump rope jumper as that cute face.
The number of jump ropes? I'm afraid I can't win. I'll give you two azukis.
Two azukis? What do you mean?
Oh, my God, she wanted azukis so bad.
Seriously, I'll never make it. I can count them with my pretty face.
Let's go. Mr. Himura, are you okay in that position?
Let's go. Get ready.
Here we go.
Okay, I can go. Go, go, go, go!
I can go.
They're coming.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, my God!
Oh, man, the camera is overwhelming!
Why can't I do it?
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Five. - Four.
Four. - Four.
Three.
Last Last
Cute
Lalalala
What's that "cute"?
This is by far the most impressive jump rope I've ever seen.
Yoda couldn't jump rope.
Just jump rope.
Just jump rope?
I don't know, it's just getting harder and harder to do it year by year.
It's been a while since I've flown.
I still don't know...
I still don't know.
If you look at the pictures
First of all, how many times did he jump rope?
Yoda did 30.
Thirty.
Yakubo did 93.
Yakubo 93 times.
Oh no!
They've already hit the prepress core.
That's why...
Is this going to be really difficult?
Unless Yakubo makes a really weird face.
Otherwise, I can't do it.
What?
But I don't get it.
Let's start with the first one.
Let's take a look.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Yoda's not good.
What do you think?
On the contrary...
What's the matter?
He's so cute!
It's cute, just a little bit.
It's cute with a little bit of humor.
It's cute with a little bit
There's no point in being cute with a little bit of chop!
Yes, it is.
It's just a little bit cute.
A lot of diversity.
So, of course, the photos didn't turn the tables.
Yakubo wins!
The rock team got 2 points!
Oh no!
This is a little bad.
This is very bad!
They had the disadvantage of jumping rope.
It can't be helped.
Just one more time.
What?
One more time.
What do you mean you can't do it?
You're kidding.
It's just caught on my skirt from now on.
It just got caught in my skirt.
I just got caught in your skirt.
What, you came out here and you couldn't do it once?
You used to be able to?
I used to be able to.
But as the years went by, I couldn't do it anymore.
But from now on...
I don't know...
If I play a female boxer in a drama or a movie, I'll be in trouble.
What should I do?
Shan shan shan!
Yakubo should fly like a boxer!
wireru
me
Unchanging quiet sea
The sun and the stick, the endless shadows move
Why are you the only one not here?
I heard it from somewhere
Auldis from the caledio
Just the passage of time is so sad
I didn't even notice the happiness in front of me
The café terrace that no longer exists
No one stopped where it used to be
That summer day in the city, like a ripple coming and going
You're not going, are you?
The beach where we walked together, I wanted our footprints to continue
I still love you.
No one ever forgets.
That's why we get over it
But for some reason, I can't stop thinking about you
I reach out my hand
I hold out my hand to you In the sunlight I see the afterimage of my youth
I can't stop thinking about that summer.
That day, the stinging waves came and went
I won't go, will I?
the beach where we walked together
I wanted our footprints to continue
I still love you
My good life is eternal
I can't stop the endless overflow of
The feelings I had back then
I can't stop loving you
Let me stay just a little longer
In the comfortable place in my memories
Aaaaah! Watch out!
It's coming, it's coming! You can't do this!
Come on, Evie.
Aahhh!
Smile please, smile please.
Oh, my God! It's so hard!
Blu-ray & DVD of Nogizaka46 11th Year Birthday Live is now available!
Tickets to watch the Under Live streaming are now on sale!
I'm Arno Nakanishi and I recently started buying a hamster named Rolls Royce!
Subscribe to my channel!